In this lesson, we're going to
be talking about Apple Events. And
one of the most important aspects
of Apple Events is the new M3 chip.
When users go to render video or use
an application like Invedio's AI
to make money or other wise, and customers
that are happy, users want to be sure
they're using the very best product
out on the market. And the
amount of trust that users put in Apple is
why we're here. Likewise, businesses need
to invest in their infrastructure and purchase
many software applications, they don't
just want to be able to have their business run
They want it to run better than anyone else. Apple
takes that into consideration when designing
everything and that creates new values.
Value is everything to the Apple design
It is a part of the apple experience.
So, what makes Apple's M3
the best?
the M3 chip is Apple's newest most
powerful piece of silicone ever
It performs better than any other
leading chip on the market and it
earns its right as the fastest. It's
no longer dependent on external factors
but is dependent upon the rate at
which Apple innovates
and it's capable of rendering video
creations using CAD and other 3D softwares.
unlike anything we've seen before
no matter the complexity in design
The M3 chip is the future of creativity
and makes Apple the leader in production
Apple is also proud to announce
it has partnered with Austin Witt
He is a leader in innovative localization
tactics and capable of multiple workflows
much like that of the new M3 chip.
He can render, edit, time, and QC captions
He is familiar with diverse work environments
and has a basic understanding of ASL as well
as several years of Spanish and a
degree in film and political science.